import { Question } from '@/src/types/questions'

export const food: Question[] = [
  {
    "question": "What is the Kanji for \"gohan\"?",
    "options": [
      "ご飯",
      "麦酒",
      "葡萄酒",
      "お酒"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ご飯"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the Katakana for \"juusu\"?",
    "options": [
      "ジュース",
      "サラダ",
      "ハム",
      "コーヒー"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ジュース"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the Katakana for \"miruku\"?",
    "options": [
      "ミルク",
      "ジュース",
      "ゴハン",
      "チーズ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ミルク"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"miruku\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "みるく",
      "こうちゃ",
      "さかな",
      "はむ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "みるく"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the Katakana for \"wain\"?",
    "options": [
      "ワイン",
      "パン",
      "ニク",
      "ミズ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ワイン"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"koohii\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "こーひー",
      "ちーず",
      "ぱすた",
      "さらだ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "こーひー"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese (romanji) word for \"Water\"?",
    "options": [
      "mizu",
      "hamu",
      "osake",
      "miruku"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "mizu"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"koohii\"?",
    "options": [
      "Coffee",
      "Pasta",
      "Meat",
      "Salad"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Coffee"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the Katakana for \"mizu\"?",
    "options": [
      "ミズ",
      "ニク",
      "ゴハン",
      "サラダ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ミズ"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the Katakana for \"sarada\"?",
    "options": [
      "サラダ",
      "ミルク",
      "ニク",
      "ハム"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "サラダ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Kanji for \"mizu\"?",
    "options": [
      "水",
      "葡萄酒",
      "紅茶",
      "珈琲"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "水"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese (romanji) word for \"Milk\"?",
    "options": [
      "miruku",
      "juusu",
      "koohii",
      "koucha"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "miruku"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"koucha\"?",
    "options": [
      "Black Tea",
      "Coffee",
      "Alcohol",
      "Salad"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Black Tea"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the Katakana for \"niku\"?",
    "options": [
      "ニク",
      "ジュース",
      "ビール",
      "パン"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ニク"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese (romanji) word for \"Black Tea\"?",
    "options": [
      "koucha",
      "mizu",
      "niku",
      "gohan"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "koucha"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"juusu\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "じゅーす",
      "にく",
      "こーひー",
      "みず"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "じゅーす"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Kanji for \"koohii\"?",
    "options": [
      "珈琲",
      "麦酒",
      "葡萄酒",
      "肉"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "珈琲"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the Katakana for \"chiizu\"?",
    "options": [
      "チーズ",
      "コウチャ",
      "サラダ",
      "パスタ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "チーズ"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the Katakana for \"koucha\"?",
    "options": [
      "コウチャ",
      "ニク",
      "サラダ",
      "チーズ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "コウチャ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Kanji for \"wain\"?",
    "options": [
      "葡萄酒",
      "紅茶",
      "肉",
      "麦酒"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "葡萄酒"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"pan\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "ぱん",
      "さらだ",
      "さかな",
      "みず"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ぱん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"hamu\"?",
    "options": [
      "Ham",
      "Alcohol",
      "Pasta",
      "Cheese"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Ham"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"juusu\"?",
    "options": [
      "Juice",
      "Coffee",
      "Salad",
      "Pasta"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Juice"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"chiizu\"?",
    "options": [
      "Cheese",
      "Pasta",
      "Beer",
      "Coffee"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Cheese"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the Katakana for \"koohii\"?",
    "options": [
      "コーヒー",
      "ミルク",
      "ビール",
      "ゴハン"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "コーヒー"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"sarada\"?",
    "options": [
      "Salad",
      "Beer",
      "Ham",
      "Water"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Salad"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese (romanji) word for \"Wine\"?",
    "options": [
      "wain",
      "niku",
      "biiru",
      "miruku"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "wain"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the Katakana for \"pasuta\"?",
    "options": [
      "パスタ",
      "オサケ",
      "ゴハン",
      "ハム"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "パスタ"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the Katakana for \"gohan\"?",
    "options": [
      "ゴハン",
      "ミルク",
      "ハム",
      "コウチャ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ゴハン"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Kanji for \"miruku\"?",
    "options": [
      "牛乳",
      "珈琲",
      "水",
      "お酒"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "牛乳"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"biiru\"?",
    "options": [
      "Beer",
      "Fish",
      "Cheese",
      "Coffee"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Beer"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"wain\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "わいん",
      "こーひー",
      "ぱすた",
      "おさけ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "わいん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"gohan\"?",
    "options": [
      "Rice",
      "Water",
      "Salad",
      "Ham"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Rice"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"pasuta\"?",
    "options": [
      "Pasta",
      "Salad",
      "Beer",
      "Cheese"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Pasta"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"hamu\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "はむ",
      "こうちゃ",
      "わいん",
      "ぱすた"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "はむ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese (romanji) word for \"Alcohol\"?",
    "options": [
      "osake",
      "miruku",
      "sarada",
      "niku"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "osake"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"chiizu\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "ちーず",
      "こーひー",
      "びーる",
      "ぱん"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ちーず"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the Katakana for \"sakana\"?",
    "options": [
      "サカナ",
      "ニク",
      "パン",
      "ワイン"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "サカナ"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the Katakana for \"hamu\"?",
    "options": [
      "ハム",
      "ジュース",
      "オサケ",
      "ゴハン"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ハム"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the Katakana for \"biiru\"?",
    "options": [
      "ビール",
      "サカナ",
      "オサケ",
      "サラダ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ビール"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Kanji for \"osake\"?",
    "options": [
      "お酒",
      "葡萄酒",
      "麦酒",
      "水"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "お酒"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese (romanji) word for \"Pasta\"?",
    "options": [
      "pasuta",
      "hamu",
      "gohan",
      "osake"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "pasuta"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"mizu\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "みず",
      "はむ",
      "こうちゃ",
      "ぱすた"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "みず"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese (romanji) word for \"Rice\"?",
    "options": [
      "gohan",
      "juusu",
      "niku",
      "wain"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "gohan"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese (romanji) word for \"Bread\"?",
    "options": [
      "pan",
      "osake",
      "koucha",
      "chiizu"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "pan"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese (romanji) word for \"Ham\"?",
    "options": [
      "hamu",
      "sarada",
      "juusu",
      "osake"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "hamu"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese (romanji) word for \"Fish\"?",
    "options": [
      "sakana",
      "pan",
      "osake",
      "koucha"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "sakana"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"niku\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "にく",
      "みず",
      "じゅーす",
      "みるく"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "にく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"wain\"?",
    "options": [
      "Wine",
      "Fish",
      "Coffee",
      "Alcohol"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Wine"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"pan\"?",
    "options": [
      "Bread",
      "Pasta",
      "Cheese",
      "Water"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Bread"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Kanji for \"niku\"?",
    "options": [
      "肉",
      "水",
      "紅茶",
      "ご飯"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "肉"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"pasuta\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "ぱすた",
      "ちーず",
      "こーひー",
      "みず"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ぱすた"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese (romanji) word for \"Salad\"?",
    "options": [
      "sarada",
      "miruku",
      "wain",
      "gohan"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "sarada"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"miruku\"?",
    "options": [
      "Milk",
      "Beer",
      "Bread",
      "Salad"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Milk"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"osake\"?",
    "options": [
      "Alcohol",
      "Milk",
      "Juice",
      "Black Tea"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Alcohol"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"mizu\"?",
    "options": [
      "Water",
      "Black Tea",
      "Wine",
      "Juice"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Water"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"osake\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "おさけ",
      "はむ",
      "さかな",
      "ぱすた"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "おさけ"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the Katakana for \"pan\"?",
    "options": [
      "パン",
      "コウチャ",
      "ゴハン",
      "チーズ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "パン"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese (romanji) word for \"Juice\"?",
    "options": [
      "juusu",
      "sarada",
      "wain",
      "niku"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "juusu"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese (romanji) word for \"Cheese\"?",
    "options": [
      "chiizu",
      "wain",
      "sarada",
      "hamu"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "chiizu"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Kanji for \"biiru\"?",
    "options": [
      "麦酒",
      "水",
      "牛乳",
      "葡萄酒"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "麦酒"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"koucha\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "こうちゃ",
      "にく",
      "びーる",
      "はむ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "こうちゃ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Kanji for \"koucha\"?",
    "options": [
      "紅茶",
      "魚",
      "水",
      "麦酒"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "紅茶"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"sakana\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "さかな",
      "ぱん",
      "びーる",
      "みるく"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "さかな"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the Katakana for \"osake\"?",
    "options": [
      "オサケ",
      "チーズ",
      "ミズ",
      "ゴハン"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "オサケ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese (romanji) word for \"Beer\"?",
    "options": [
      "biiru",
      "koohii",
      "gohan",
      "hamu"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "biiru"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Kanji for \"sakana\"?",
    "options": [
      "魚",
      "水",
      "葡萄酒",
      "紅茶"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "魚"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"niku\"?",
    "options": [
      "Meat",
      "Milk",
      "Wine",
      "Salad"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Meat"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese (romanji) word for \"Meat\"?",
    "options": [
      "niku",
      "osake",
      "wain",
      "koohii"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "niku"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"sarada\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "さらだ",
      "こうちゃ",
      "ごはん",
      "ぱん"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "さらだ"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"gohan\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "ごはん",
      "ちーず",
      "ぱん",
      "おさけ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ごはん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"sakana\"?",
    "options": [
      "Fish",
      "Cheese",
      "Rice",
      "Wine"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Fish"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese (romanji) word for \"Coffee\"?",
    "options": [
      "koohii",
      "miruku",
      "chiizu",
      "juusu"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "koohii"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"biiru\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "びーる",
      "にく",
      "さらだ",
      "さかな"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "びーる"
  }
];

export default food;